<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
<channel>
<title>revRSS - Newswires</title>
<link>https://www.revrss.com/newswires.xml</link>
<atom:link href="https://www.revrss.com/newswires.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
<atom:link href="https://pubsubhubbub.appspot.com/" rel="hub"/>
<description>Feed of reverse stock splits found on newswires</description>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:00:11 GMT</pubDate>
<lastBuildDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 21:00:11 GMT</lastBuildDate>
<item>
<title>Blue Moon Announces Proposed Share Consolidation</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 03 Mar 2025 14:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/03/03/3035770/0/en/Blue-Moon-Announces-Proposed-Share-Consolidation.html</link>
<description>BLUE MOON ANNOUNCES PROPOSED SHARE CONSOLIDATION</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lichen China Limited Announces Effective Date of Reverse Stock Split and Name Change</title>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 13:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/lichen-china-limited-announces-effective-date-of-reverse-stock-split-and-name-change-302386726.html</link>
<description>XIAMEN, China: XIAMEN, China, Feb. 27, 2025 /PRNewswire/ -- Lichen China Limited (Nasdaq: LICN) ("Lichen China" or the "Company"), a dedicated financial and taxation service provider in China today announced the date of effectiveness and the ratio of a forthcoming reverse stock split (the "Reverse Split") of the Company's ordinary shares (the "Ordinary Shares"). On February 12, 2025, the Company announced, on a Current Report on Form 6-K, the voting results from the annual meeting of shareholders (the "Meeting") held on February 10, 2025. At the Meeting, shareholders voted upon and approved Proposal 2 to effect a Reverse Split with a ratio of not less than one-for-twenty and not more than one-for-two-hundred within one year after the date of passing of the resolution, with the exact ratio to be set at a whole number within this range as determined by the Company's board of directors (the "Board") in its sole discretion.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Venus Concept Announces 1-for-11 Reverse Stock Split</title>
<pubDate>Thu, 27 Feb 2025 12:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/02/27/3033743/0/en/Venus-Concept-Announces-1-for-11-Reverse-Stock-Split.html</link>
<description>TORONTO, Feb. 27, 2025 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Venus Concept Inc. (“Venus Concept” or the “Company”) (NASDAQ: VERO), a global medical aesthetic technology leader, today announced that it will effect a 1-for-11 reverse stock split of the Company’s issued and outstanding common stock (the “Reverse Stock Split”). The Reverse Stock Split will be effective at 5:00 p.m. Eastern Standard Time on March 3, 2025. The Company’s common stock is expected to begin trading on The Nasdaq Capital Market on a split-adjusted basis at the open of trading on March 4, 2025.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>AEON Biopharma, Inc. Announces Reverse Stock Split</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 19:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/02/24/3031446/0/en/AEON-Biopharma-Inc-Announces-Reverse-Stock-Split.html</link>
<description>IRVINE, Calif., Feb. 24, 2025 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- AEON Biopharma, Inc. (NYSE: AEON) (the “Company”), a clinical-stage biopharmaceutical company focused on developing a botulinum toxin complex under a 351(k) biosimilar pathway, today announced that the Company’s Board of Directors approved a 1-for-72 reverse stock split (the “Reverse Stock Split”) of the Company’s common stock, par value $0.0001 (the “Common Stock”), to increase the selling price of the Company’s Common Stock in order to maintain compliance with the requirements and policies of the NYSE American LLC (the “NYSE American”).</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Karyopharm Announces 1-for-15 Reverse Stock Split</title>
<pubDate>Mon, 24 Feb 2025 13:40:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.prnewswire.com/news-releases/karyopharm-announces-1-for-15-reverse-stock-split-302383407.html</link>
<description>NEWTON, Mass.: NEWTON, Mass., Feb. 24, 2025 /PRNewswire/ -- Karyopharm Therapeutics Inc. (Nasdaq: KPTI), a commercial-stage pharmaceutical company pioneering novel cancer therapies, today announced that it will implement a 1-for-15 reverse stock split of the issued shares of the Company's common stock ("Reverse Stock Split"), effective at 5:00 p.m. Eastern Time on February 25, 2025. The Reverse Stock Split was approved by the Company's stockholders at the Company's Special Meeting of Stockholders held on January 30, 2025, with the final ratio subsequently determined by the Company's Board of Directors. One of the primary goals of the Reverse Stock Split is to increase the per-share market price of the Company's common stock to enable the Company to regain compliance with the minimum bid price requirement for continued listing on the Nasdaq Global Select Market.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>SaverOne Implements Change in Ratio of Shares to ADSs to Meet Nasdaq Minimum Bid Price Requirement</title>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 22:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/02/21/3030722/0/en/SaverOne-Implements-Change-in-Ratio-of-Shares-to-ADSs-to-Meet-Nasdaq-Minimum-Bid-Price-Requirement.html</link>
<description>Petah Tikvah, Israel, Feb. 21, 2025 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- SaverOne 2014 Ltd. (Nasdaq: SVRE, TASE: SVRE), On February 20, 2025, SaverOne 2014 Ltd. received a letter from the Listing Qualifications Department of The Nasdaq Stock Market LLC, notifying the Company that it was not in compliance with Nasdaq Listing Rule 5550(a)(2) which requires listed companies to maintain a minimum bid price of $1.00 per share. Normally, a company would be afforded a 180-calendar day period to demonstrate compliance with the Minimum Bid Price Requirement. However, pursuant to recently enacted Nasdaq regulations, the Company is not eligible for any compliance period) because the Company has effected a reverse stock split over the prior one-year period. The Company’s ADSs are subject to delisting from Nasdaq unless the Company requests an appeal of this determination by February 27, 2025.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>China SXT Pharmaceuticals, Inc. Announces Share Consolidation</title>
<pubDate>Fri, 21 Feb 2025 17:35:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/02/21/3030608/0/en/China-SXT-Pharmaceuticals-Inc-Announces-Share-Consolidation.html</link>
<description>TAIZHOU, China, Feb. 21, 2025 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- China SXT Pharmaceutics, Inc. (Nasdaq: SXTC) (the “Company” or “SXTC”),  a specialty pharmaceutical company focusing on the research, development, manufacturing, marketing, and sales of Traditional Chinese Medicine Pieces (“TCMPs”), including Advanced TCMPs (Directly-Oral TCMP and After-Soaking-Oral TCMP), fine TCMPs, regular TCMPs, and TCM Homologous Supplements (“TCMHS”), today announced that it will effect a share consolidation of its ordinary shares at a ratio of 1-for-8, effective on February 25, 2025 (the “Share Consolidation”). The Company’s ordinary shares are expected to begin trading on a post-consolidation basis at the open of the market session on February 25, 2025. Upon the market opening on February 25, 2025, the Company’s ordinary shares will continue to be traded on The Nasdaq Stock Market under the symbol “SXTC” with the new CUSIP number G2161P157.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Lottery.com Announces Positive Results From Annual Shareholder Meeting</title>
<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 23:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/02/20/3030171/0/en/Lottery-com-Announces-Positive-Results-From-Annual-Shareholder-Meeting.html</link>
<description>Company Board Votes Not to Proceed With Reverse Stock Split Company Board Votes Not to Proceed With Reverse Stock Split</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Jolt Health Inc. Announces Share Consolidation</title>
<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 22:45:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.accessnewswire.com/newsroom/en/healthcare-and-pharmaceutical/jolt-health-inc-announces-share-consolidation-988856</link>
<description>VANCOUVER, BC / ACCESS Newswire / February 20, 2025 / Jolt Health Inc. ("JOLT" and or "the Company") (CSE:JOLT)(FSE:G1Q0) announces it intends to proceed with a consolidation of its common shares (each, a "Share") on the basis of twenty (20) pre-consolidation Shares for one (1) post-consolidation Share (the "Consolidation").</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>60 Degrees Pharmaceuticals, Inc. Announces 1:5 Reverse Stock Split</title>
<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 15:36:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/02/20/3029853/0/en/60-Degrees-Pharmaceuticals-Inc-Announces-1-5-Reverse-Stock-Split.html</link>
<description>60 Degrees Pharma (SXTP) announces a 1-for-5 reverse stock split, effective Feb. 24, 2025, to meet Nasdaq's $1.00 minimum bid price requirement.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>HWH International Inc. Announces Reverse Stock Split</title>
<pubDate>Thu, 20 Feb 2025 13:50:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/02/20/3029680/0/en/HWH-International-Inc-Announces-Reverse-Stock-Split.html</link>
<description>BETHESDA, MD, Feb. 20, 2025 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- HWH International Inc. (the “Company”) (NASDAQ: HWH), a purpose-driven lifestyle company, today announced a 1-for-5 reverse stock split of the Company’s common stock to become effective at 9:00 a.m. (Eastern Time) on February 24, 2025. The Company’s common stock is expected to begin trading on a split-adjusted basis when the markets open on February 24, 2025, under the existing trading symbol “HWH.”</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>GRI Bio Announces Reverse Stock Split</title>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 21:05:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/02/19/3029146/0/en/GRI-Bio-Announces-Reverse-Stock-Split.html</link>
<description>GRI’s common stock is expected to begin trading on a post-split adjusted basis on February 24, 2025</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>CNS Pharmaceuticals Announces Reverse Stock Split</title>
<pubDate>Wed, 19 Feb 2025 14:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.accessnewswire.com/newsroom/en/healthcare-and-pharmaceutical/cns-pharmaceuticals-announces-reverse-stock-split-987344</link>
<description>HOUSTON, TX / ACCESS Newswire / February 19, 2025 / CNS Pharmaceuticals, Inc. (NASDAQ:CNSP)("CNS" or the "Company"), a biopharmaceutical company specializing in the development of novel treatments for primary and metastatic cancers in the brain and central nervous system, today announced a 1-for-50 reverse split of its common stock.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Datametrex Announces Effective Date for Share Consolidation</title>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 22:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.accessnewswire.com/newsroom/en/computers-technology-and-internet/datametrex-announces-effective-date-for-share-consolidation-987330</link>
<description>TORONTO, ON /ACCESS Newswire/ February 18, 2025 /Datametrex AI Limited (the "Company" or "Datametrex") (TSXV:DM)(FSE:D4G)(OTCQB:DTMXF) announces that, further to the Company's news release dated February 6, 2025,effectiveat the opening on February 19, 2025, the common shares of the Company ("Shares") will commence trading on the TSX Venture Exchange ("TSXV") on a consolidated basis of one (1) post-consolidation share for every thirty (30) pre-consolidation shares (the "Consolidation"). The Company</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Know Labs Announces Reverse Stock Split Effective February 19, 2025</title>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>http://www.businesswire.com/news/home/20250218705498/en/Know-Labs-Announces-Reverse-Stock-Split-Effective-February-19-2025/?feedref=JjAwJuNHiystnCoBq_hl-RtwWlzPOLIHNbADHi-l3taAELgUeC8Apx51rXHivzq_WJT50v2g3Ei-19qH0fyPszGrim8IhAkVNXbaI1AGppOzkqEXpa07kut2m9xviGvGqdHRimgf3pq4HvtCi4Rp6w==</link>
<description>SEATTLE--(BUSINESS WIRE)--Know Labs, Inc. (previously NYSE American: KNW, now OTC Pink Markets: KNWN), a pioneering leader in the development and application of radio frequency dielectric spectroscopy (RFDS), announced today a 1 for 40 reverse stock split of its authorized and issued and outstanding shares of common stock. The reverse stock split was announced on February 18, 2025. The reverse stock split will be effective as of the morning of February 19, 2025, and the Company’s common stock w</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Aptose Announces Reverse Share Split</title>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 21:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/02/18/3028350/35575/en/Aptose-Announces-Reverse-Share-Split.html</link>
<description>Aptose Announces Reverse Share Split</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Windtree Therapeutics, Inc. Announces Reverse Stock Split</title>
<pubDate>Tue, 18 Feb 2025 13:00:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/02/18/3027760/0/en/Windtree-Therapeutics-Inc-Announces-Reverse-Stock-Split.html</link>
<description>WARRINGTON, Pa., Feb. 18, 2025 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Windtree Therapeutics, Inc. (NasdaqCM: WINT) (“Windtree” or the “Company”), a biotechnology company focused on advancing early and late-stage innovative therapies for critical conditions and diseases, announces that its board of directors has approved a 1-for-50 reverse stock split of the Company’s common stock. The Company’s stockholders approved the reverse stock split proposal at the Company’s Special Meeting of Stockholders held on February 3, 2025. The stockholders granted the board of directors the authority to determine the exact split ratio and when to proceed with the reverse stock split.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Comstock Announces Reverse Stock Split</title>
<pubDate>Fri, 14 Feb 2025 21:32:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/02/14/3026893/0/en/Comstock-Announces-Reverse-Stock-Split.html</link>
<description>VIRGINIA CITY, Nev., Feb. 14, 2025 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- Comstock Inc. ("Comstock") (NYSE American: LODE), a leading innovator of renewable energy-enabling technologies that contribute to energy abundance by efficiently extracting and converting under-utilized natural resources today announced a reverse split of its common stock, $0.000666 par value (“Common Stock”), at a ratio of 1-for-10 (the “Reverse Split”), effective February 24, 2025, and that the Common Stock will begin trading on a split-adjusted basis when the market opens on February 25, 2025, resulting in approximately 23,767,578 shares outstanding.</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Corporate Update - Share Consolidation and ICSID Annulment</title>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 23:16:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.accessnewswire.com/newsroom/en/metals-and-mining/corporate-update-share-consolidation-and-icsid-annulment-985017</link>
<description>LONDON, UK /ACCESS Newswire/ February 13, 2025 /Gabriel Resources Ltd. (TSXV:GBU)("Gabriel" or the "Company") announces the following corporate update on its proposed 10:1 share consolidation and the ICSID annulment proceedings, including recent developments concerning the provisional stay of enforcement and the procedural calendar. Effective Date of Share Consolidation Further to the Company's press release on December 20, 2024, Gabriel has received approval of the TSX Venture Exchange (the "TSXV")</description>
</item>
<item>
<title>Mullen Automotive Inc. Announces Reverse Stock Split Effective Feb. 18, 2025</title>
<pubDate>Thu, 13 Feb 2025 16:30:00 GMT</pubDate>
<link>https://www.globenewswire.com/news-release/2025/02/13/3026088/0/en/Mullen-Automotive-Inc-Announces-Reverse-Stock-Split-Effective-Feb-18-2025.html</link>
<description>BREA, Calif., Feb. 13, 2025 (GLOBE NEWSWIRE) -- via IBN -- Mullen Automotive Inc. (NASDAQ: MULN) (“Mullen” or the “Company”), an electric vehicle (“EV”) manufacturer, announced today that it will effect a 1-for-60 reverse stock split (“Reverse Stock Split”) of its common stock, par value $0.001 per share (“Common Stock”), that will become effective on Feb. 18, 2025, at 12:01 a.m. Eastern Time. The Common Stock will continue to trade on The Nasdaq Capital Market (“Nasdaq”) under the existing symbol MULN and will begin trading on a split-adjusted basis when the market opens on Feb. 18, 2025. The new CUSIP number for the Common Stock following the Reverse Stock Split will be 62526P604.</description>
</item>
</channel>
</rss>